reneweconomy.com.au 2018-03-23

# Privacy Policy : RenewEconomy

This privacy policy applies to all personal information collected by us through the website, or through other interactions with you. In this privacy policy, the terms “we”, “us” and “ours” refers to Reneweconomy Pty Ltd and the Reneweconomy Trust. The term “Website” means the website located at [www.reneweconomy.com.au](http://www.reneweconomy.com.au/).

## How to contact us about privacy

Your privacy is very important to us. For that reason, please read the following details carefully and get in contact with us if you have any questions. You can contact us at PO Box 881, Neutral Bay, NSW 2089 or at info@reneweconomy.com.au

## Collection and Purpose

We may collect personal information from you in the course of your use of the website and if you input any personal information into the website. In addition, we also collect cookies and other tracking information from your computer, which enables us to tell when you use the website and also to help customise your website experience.

We collect this personal information so that we can continue to improve the service we provide to our users, to provide marketing communications in relation to our business and where relevant to provide you with ongoing news and information. We may also collect personal information if you choose to register on the website. The purpose of such information is clear from the context in which it is collected, but may include to receive updates and newsletters from us if you so elect as well as to receive marketing communications from us from time to time.

Some provision of personal information is optional. However, if you do not provide us with certain types of personal information, you may be unable to enjoy the full functionality of the website.

## Disclosure

Our personnel (including our employees, contractors and agents engaged by us) may have access to personal information that you provide and may access it for purposes that include the audit of content on the website. We will not sell your personal information to an unrelated third party without your consent. We customarily do not disclose personal information to unrelated third parties without your consent except (a) where such disclosure is incidental to your use of the website; (b) where such disclosure is required for us to provide products and services for you, such as financial institutions, our agents, business partners, joint venture entities or partners; (c) if we deem it necessary to conduct any investigation into you or your activities, for example in relation to a possible breach of our terms or use; or (d) if required or permitted by law. You consent to us disclosing your personal information for the purpose of any of the above listed exceptions.

## Access and correction

National Privacy Principle 6 of the Australian Privacy Act allows you to get access to, and correct, the personal information we hold about you in certain circumstances. If you would like to obtain such access, please contact us on the details set out above.

## Security

We take reasonable steps to attempt to ensure the security of your personal information.

## Your warranty

If at any time you provide personal or other information about someone other than yourself, you warrant that you have that person’s consent to provide such information for the purpose specified.

In the event that our business or the website is ever sold or transferred, we reserve the right to transfer to the extent permissible at law our user databases, together with any personal information and non-personal information contained in those databases.

## Transfer out of Australia

We may use software or service providers based outside of Australia (including but not limited to website hosting and database management). For that reason, we may transfer part or all data on the website (including personal information) to service providers based outside of Australia. You hereby consent to this transfer.

## Authorisation

By using the website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us in accordance with this privacy policy.

## Changes to this policy

If there is any change to our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
